co-parenting is hard co-parenting is
rough
i didn't know what petty was until i had
to co-parent
we argue over the pettiest garbage it's
just
we it's just like we're contractually
obligated to do it now
and it's it's it's a no way to live no
way to live
try to avoid that if you ever have to i
got an email from her like several
months back
about our son and the subject of the
email was
washing hands
this woman okay all right
low washing hands what do i need to know
about washing hands
and she said um ethan says
that at your house he doesn't have to
wash his hands when he pees
only if he poops
[Music]
but at our house he always has to wash
his hands
and i feel like this has been confusing
him
yeah i'd just be best if you adopted the
same rules
at your house okay okay
okay i thank you i of course
of course i make him i i make him wash
his hands he's just
lying to you he's poor he will say
anything to get out of washing his hands
[Laughter]
it's called triangulation all kids of
divorce do it when he's at my house and
i me you know what he says to me he's
like
but mommy doesn't make me wash my hands
and you know what i don't send you an
email about it i just make him wash his
hands
[Applause]
this feels like an unnecessary step
but okay i'll play let's say i don't
make him wash his hands
when he pees only if he poops
you're worried that that has been
confusing him
[Laughter]
the other morning he said to me my mommy
and jeff sleep naked
which one of those two things do you
think is causing more confusion in our
toddler's life babe
[Laughter]
no i've talked to him about jeff okay
of course i have and he's smarter than
you think he is give him some credits
all right i've talked to him about jeff
and i feel like he has a good handle on
the situation
well which is it huh is he a a
four-year-old savant
who can understand all the complexities
of adult love and parental divorce
or is he a that doesn't know how
to wash his hands
because i feel like you got to pick one
you're welcome man
my kid really said that to me though
like first thing in the morning i was
just all i was doing i was like
we just woke up i was trying to get him
out of his pajamas i was like buddy we
gotta get out of our sleepy clothes and
get into our play clothes and he came
right back at me with my mommy and jeff
sleep naked
kid it is 7 30 in the morning man
are you starting on me this early
it's gonna be a long day kid
and it was
it was a very long day and somehow i
got through without sending you a whiny
little email about it
uh yeah ethan says that at your house
you guys sleep naked but at
our house everyone wears pajamas
just a rule that we have
also anyone named jeff has to sleep on
the couch
[Laughter]
i just feel like this has been confusing
him
if you could adopt the same rules at
your place
it'll be great
you